LAHIRU MADUSHAN



About Me

Keen to work as a trustworthy team member and work hard to achieve targets for the success of any organization by utilizing my educational & professional experience

Contact

- +019-676-4038 / +9477-384-2096
- hiru.m9012@gmail.com
- https://klm90.000webhostapp.com/
- www.linkedin.com/in/lahiru-madushan90
- NTI International University, Persian Perdana BBN Putra Nilai

Programming Languages

Java

C++

Python







Web Technologies

- HTML5
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- ReactJS

Experience

Assistant Auto Electrical Engineer

Nimbus Venture Pvt Ltd

Dec 2020 - Jan 2022

- Supervisory activities of FMS, DMS, TMS of Cloud Based Vehicle data driven solution (SAAS)
- GPS Trackers installation with Sensors (**Busses, Cars, Lorries with freezers, Bikes, Road Trucks**)
- PCB Design for Customer Issues, Documentation, Sensor Calibrations, debugging, Firmware updating.
- New Product Innovations, Bug Fixing

Assistant Electrical Engineer

Richardson Technologies Pvt Ltd

July 2018 – July 2020

- Smart Street Light Project Supervision at Colombo, Sri Lanka (3 Feeder Piller Designs)
- Streetlights and Poles Survey around 15000 poles from 3 months (estimated time 6 month)
- Mapping streetlights in Google map- Average mapping per day is 90 poles per 8 Hours,
- Testing of Street lights, Project handling and Labor management.
- CCTV Installations.

Education

INTI International University Expected Graduation: Dec 2024

Diploma in Computer Science (Cybersecurity)

- Cumulative GPA: 3.50/4.00
- 2 consecutive Dean's List for excellent academic achievement

University of the West of England Completed: Dec 2020

Master of Engineering Electrical and Electronic (General Degree)

SLIATE-Sri Lanka

Completed: Nov 2016

Diploma in Electrical and Electronic Engineering (Electrical)

Cumulative GPA=2.808/4.00

Database Languages

- MYSQL
- MongoDB

Softwares

- Microsoft Packages
- Microsoft Visio
- MATLAB
- Arduino
- Proteus
- R

Interests

- Innovations
- Guitaring
- traveling
- movies
- music

References

Assistant Professor: Dr. Asokan Vasudevan Contact: +6 019-6219975 INTI International University

UNIVERSITY ACHIEVEMENTS

Online CV

100% contributor to the project. (https://klm90.000webhostapp.com/) -Mar 2024

Coding with HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Online Order Tracking System

80% contributor to the project.

•Coding the Project using C++

Website design for a Juice Shop

100% contributor to the project. (https://4efdaa26.pennyjuicenewux.pages.dev/) -Mar 2024

Coding with HTML, CSS

Inventory Management System for Retail Shop

90% contributor to the project.

-Nov 2023

-Mar 2024

•Coding the Project using Java GUI, JDBC, MYSQL

Library Management System for INTI

60% contributor to the project.

-Mar 2023

●Coding the Project using C++

CO-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

INTI International University Student Helper

Nilai, Negeri Sembilan Dec 2023 - Now

- Manage finance team to getting leads of international students (coordinates and guidance)
- •Calling to International Students and collecting data
- Duplication data Checking